(Sheldon:)How could you for a moment think
that my favorite amino acid is glutamine?
- He had lysine but changed it.
- Yeah.
Should have, would have,
could have, Raj.
I like to floss before I eat...
(Kripke:)...so my gum pockets
are open for new food.
(Kripke:)Ew.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Hello.
(Kripke:)How did I walk past you?
I'm Barry.
(Scene:)- Penny.
- Eh, that's not a very hot name.
I'm gonna call you "Roxanne."
(Kripke:)Ooh, pot stickers.
(Howard:)Suddenly, I'm looking pretty good, huh?
(Sheldon:)So, uh, Kripke,
I was wondering if there's any chance...
(Sheldon:)...you could get me some time
on the Open Science Grid computer?
(Leonard:)No.
(Sheldon:)No?
(Sheldon:)But we're friends.
I'm sorry. No, my friend.